
		// /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
		//
		// 					      Hero Names
		//
		// /////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
		"npc_dota_hero_treant"	"★Petey Penguin★"
		"npc_dota_hero_shadow_demon"	"★Kappa★"
		"npc_dota_hero_techies"	"★Maji★"
		"npc_dota_hero_night_stalker"	"★Void Demon★"
		"npc_dota_hero_spirit_breaker"	"★Astral Trekker★"
		"npc_dota_hero_tinker"	"★Ensign Ricky★"
		"npc_dota_hero_visage"	"★Puff★"
		"npc_dota_hero_treant_long"	"Petey Penguin the Intimidator"
		"npc_dota_hero_shadow_demon_long"	"Kappa the Bastion"
		"npc_dota_hero_techies_long"	"Maji the Persuasive"
		"npc_dota_hero_night_stalker_long"	"Void Demon"
		"npc_dota_hero_spirit_breaker_long"	"Astral Trekker the Wanderer"
		"npc_dota_hero_tinker_long"	"Ensign Ricky, Terran Marine"
		"npc_dota_hero_visage_long"	"Puff the Magic Dragon"
		"npc_dota_hero_treant_bio"	"The Intimidator, put simply, intimidates. He has the ability to belittle those who cross his angry gaze, and can set aflame his enemies to restore his allies' health. Always active, the Intimidator can automatically cripple his enemies, but sometimes he cripples himself in the process. And when all else fails, the Intimidator can intimidate over the phone...a sign of the times, I suppose.\nPrimary attribute is agility. Can learn Glare, Grill, Physical Activity and Be My Friend."
		"npc_dota_hero_shadow_demon_bio"	"A powerful creature from unknown lands, Kappa has the unique ability to channel his own power to support his allies. His unique composition allows him to continually improve his power while boosting that of his friends. Kappa also has the incredible ability to permanently transfer his improved constitution to his comrades, aiding them indefinitely for the duration of battle.\nPrimary attribute is strength. Can learn Power Flux, Speed Flux, Mind Flux and Transference."
		"npc_dota_hero_techies_bio"	"Maji's silver tongue has long convinced enemies to behave poorly when reason would dictate better judgment. With his words he is able to convince enemies to trade treasures for trash, or to relinquish credit for their accomplishments to Maji when none is rightfully due. And when words fail, well, that's what the missiles are for. \nPrimary attribute is strength. Can learn Lagmonster, Kill Steal, Swindle and High Stakes."
		"npc_dota_hero_night_stalker_bio"	"Speed hero.\n\nHistory: The orginal Useage of Dread Lord model in WC3, join DotA in version 2, got replaced by Night Stalker in DotA v5.1. \nPrimary attribute is strength. Can learn Time Void, Quake, Degen Aura and Mass Haste"
		"npc_dota_hero_spirit_breaker_bio"	"Melee hero.\n\nHistory: A very old hero, the original usage of Spirit Walker model in WC3. Got removed from DotA in version 3, probably because it's way too overpowered. \nPrimary attribute is strength. Can learn War Stomp, Entrapment, Pulverize and Giant Growth."
		"npc_dota_hero_tinker_bio"	"Ensign Ricky and his platoon were marooned during a routine patrol around the Koprulu Sector. After wandering for weeks, they finally landed on an uncharted planet, and Ensign Ricky was bravely volunteered by his comrades to scout the area and look for aid. Armed to the teeth with the latest in Terran weaponry, Ensign Ricky is an undeniable powerhouse on this primitive world.\nPrimary attribute is agility. Can learn Stim Pack, Heavy Artillery, Precision and U-247 RIFLE."
		"npc_dota_hero_visage_bio"	"Puff, the magic dragon lived by the sea\nAnd frolicked in the autumn mist in a land called Hanalei,\nLittle Jackie Paper loved that rascal Puff,\nBut then Puff ate Jackie Paper.\nThe end.\nPrimary attribute is strength. Can learn Dragon Roar, Dragon Breath, Dragon Hide and Dragon Magic."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_arc_warden"	"★Mana Fiend★"
		"npc_dota_hero_arc_warden_bio"	"The Mana Fiend is a powerful entity with the ability to manipulate the mana reserves of heroes. By tapping into the mana pools of itself and enemy heroes, the Mana Fiend has the ability to deplete an enemy's life and mystic forces.\nPrimary attribute is intelligence. Can Learn Equilibrium, Mana Rift, Osmose and Abandon."
		"npc_dota_hero_arc_warden_long"	"Mana Fiend"
		
		"npc_dota_hero_wisp"	"★Formless★"
		"npc_dota_hero_wisp_long"	"Incohatus, Formless"
		"npc_dota_hero_wisp_bio"	"Incohatus has no permanent form, but has learned to adapt to the ever-changing field of battle. He has the ability to replicate most spells perfectly, allowing him to use other heroes' abilities against themselves. With this strategy, Incohatus opens up a whole new world of possibilities, allowing him to take the best and worst of all the abilities his allies and enemies have to offer.\nPrimary attribute is intelligence. Can learn Unus, Duos, Tertius and Denique."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_beastmaster"	"★Jerry Boomerwang★"
		"npc_dota_hero_beastmaster_long"	"Jerry Boomerwang, The Fluid Engineer"
		"npc_dota_hero_beastmaster_bio"	"'Mind over matter', so they say. Using his superior intellect, Boomerwang is able to manipulate the ebb and flow of energies to wreak havoc on his enemies. As his Intelligence grows, the potency of his attacks increases, allowing him to create massive amounts of chaos to crush his opponents.\nPrimary attribute is intelligence. Can learn Brainstorm, Salad Launch, Malicious Tampering and Bowel Hydraulics."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_enigma"	"★Telekinetic Blob★"
		"npc_dota_hero_enigma_long"	"Inky, the Telekinetic Blob"
		"npc_dota_hero_enigma_bio"	"Inky the Telekinetic Blob has no weapons, but uses his powerful psychokinetic abilities to attack with the power of his mind. Flinging enemies and allies left and right, Inky will take his enemies down with, well, his enemies. Or friends. Inky's not picky.\nPrimary attribute is intelligence. Can learn Throw, Catapult, Sling and Expel."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_brewmaster"	"★Ramza Beoulve★"
		"npc_dota_hero_brewmaster_long"	"Ramza Beoulve, the tactical hero"
		"npc_dota_hero_brewmaster_bio"	"Ramza Beoulve, the true hero of the War of the Lions. Can take on a variety of job classes, making him an extremely versatile and powerful hero. The abilities he has available change depending on which job class he is currently using and how adept he is at each job. Starts as a Squire.\nPrimary Attribute Depends on job."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_rubick"	"★Lyonis★"
		"npc_dota_hero_rubick_long"	"Lyonis, the Cleric"
		"npc_dota_hero_rubick_bio"	"After months of battling the demonic hordes, the undead plague, and the Nighon warlords in Erathia, Loynis decided to take a little break during the temporary peace. Unfortunately for him, he chose a terrible place to vacation, and was thrust back onto the battlefield. Armed with his Erathian schools of magic, Loynis is ready to take up the mantle of battle once again.\nPrimary attribute is intelligence. Can learn Meteor Shower, Berserk, Magic Mirror and Prayer."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_windrunner"	"★Rawrzi★"
		"npc_dota_hero_windrunner_long"	"Rawrzi, the Pet Summoner"
		"npc_dota_hero_windrunner_bio"	"Rawrzi's pets, though cute and innocent in nature, have struck fear into the hearts of her enemies for as long as anyone can remember. A powerful beastmaster, Rawrzi's unique synergy with her legion of pets allow her to destroy even the most steadfast of citadels. She can even call on her unique power to turn both friend and foe into furry forest creatures.\nPrimary attribute is intelligence. Can learn Pets, Fix Boo-Boo, Mittens's Meow and Critters."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_sven"	"★Malragor★"
		"npc_dota_hero_sven_long"	"Malragor, the Felguard"
		"npc_dota_hero_sven_bio"	"Malragor always hated Sven for abandoning the evil ways of the Felguards and acting on his own self-righteousness. His hatred alone convinced the Burning Legion to send him to the battlefield. Armed with his trusty weapon, Fireblade, Malragor uses his rage to show everyone how a Felguard fights.\nPrimary attribute is strength. Can learn Felguard Wrath, Fireblade Strike, Strength and Honor and Overflow."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_pugna"	"★El Dorado★"
		"npc_dota_hero_pugna_long"	"El Dorado, the item master"
		"npc_dota_hero_pugna_bio"	"This incredibly greedy conqueror was looking for El Dorado, the Golden City.\nBut one day, a powerful priest cursed him.\nNow that forgotten and proud conqueror is nothing more than a simple frog.\nA talented Forge founds it and teaches it how to make armor and weapons.\nNow this forgotten creature is a powerful item master with the name of his cursed dream.\nPrimary attribute is intelligence. Can learn Item Forge, Artificial Frog, Refined Weapons and Piracy Method."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_disruptor"  "★Frash★"
		"npc_dota_hero_disruptor_long"  "Frash, the Hurricane"
		"npc_dota_hero_disruptor_bio"  "Technically it's a tornado, but hurricane just sounds so much better. Regardless, the winds of Frash are posed to lay waste to all in its path, enemy or otherwise. Able to toss and damage units with its unpredictable and powerful attacks, Hurricane Frash is an unstoppable force against both his allies and enemies. \nPrimary attribute is strength. Can learn Tempest, Cyclone, Whirlwind, and Eye of the Storm."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_nevermore"  "★CAPSLOCKFTW★"
		"npc_dota_hero_nevermore_long"  "CAPSLOCKFTW, the Offender of the Ancients"
		"npc_dota_hero_nevermore_bio"  "The Ancients have always needed defending, but one man was set on doing anything but that. Armed with naught but scathingly sarcastic wit, he brashly challenged the Ancients...and was struck down. Escaping from fiery purgatory, he outwitted Death and returned to complete his task, regardless of how many Allstars stand in his way.\nPrimary attribute is agility. Can Learn Flamer, Hax, Sarcasm, and Ban."
		
		"npc_dota_hero_omniknight"  "★Beowulf Cadmus★"
		"npc_dota_hero_omniknight_long"  "Beowulf Cadmus, the Templar"
		"npc_dota_hero_omniknight_bio"  "Beowulf stumbled upon this battlefield while searching the land of Ivalice for the Dragonkin Reis, his lost love. With his Spellblade abilities, Beowulf is a powerful swordsman with several powerful spells at his disposal, including the ability to draw upon his wounds to heavily damage his opponents and to cripple them by turning them into helpless fowl."